Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Office of the General President records, 1883-2001 IBT0017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Community Service Surveys, 1963-1964; Series 2; 1.75 Linear Feet
  - Local 844 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Local 845 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Local 847 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Local 853 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Local 856 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Local 860 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Local 868 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 22; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Local 871 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Local 872 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Local 886 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Local 890 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Local 891 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 27; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Local 893 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 17; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Local 900 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 19; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Local 908 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Local 912 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Local 915 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Local 929 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 7; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Local 933 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 24; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Local 938 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Local 952 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 1; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Local 954 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Local 960 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 3; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Local 962 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 14; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Local 964 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Local 968 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 10; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Local 971 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 27; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Local 975 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Local 977 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 13; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Local 979 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 28; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Local 983 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Local 987 Community Service Survey, 1963 July 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Local 990 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 28; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Local 992 Community Service Survey, 1963 May 29; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Local 993 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 15; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Local 996 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 24; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Local 999 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 12; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Local 1060 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 26; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Local 1076 Community Service Survey, 1963 June 10; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Local 1077 Community Service Survey, 1963 August 2; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Local 1145 Community Service Survey, 1963 September 17; Series 2 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Vice President's Papers, 1975-1993; Series 3
  Arranged chronologically. Note: after Box 7 the order restarts.
  This series contains the notes of Vice President of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Walter J. Shea, from 1975 - 1993.
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1975, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1979, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1980, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1981, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1982, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1985, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1986, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1987, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1989, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1991, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1992, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Walter J. Shea Notes - 1993, Series 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1968, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1969, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1969, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1972, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1974, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1975, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1976, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1977, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1978, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1979, Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1980, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1981, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1982, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1983, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1984, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1985, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1985, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1986, Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1987, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1994, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Walter J. Shea Daily Planner-1994, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1953-2011; Series 4
  This series contains miscellaneous files pertaining to the Office of the General President.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Photo Album of 25 Louisiana Ave NW, Washington, DC 20001, Headquarters Construction, February 24, 1953 - February 10, 1955; Series 4 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    General
    Album consists of approximately 109 of photos documenting the construction of the national headquarters for the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Photos showcase breaking ground and completion from several directions.
  - Guidelines for Conducting the Local Union Elections, 1975-1978; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration of Officers Guidelines, 2007; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa / Hall Vote, 2011; Series 4 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Photo of Teamsters Cutting Cake, ND; IBT0017 Series 4 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Department and Division Changes and Leadership, 28 March 2022; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa/Aloise Oath of Office, Undated; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Meet the Candidates, Undated; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Staffing Changes, 25 March 2022; Series 4 (Box Shared Box 36, Folder 12)